<!-- Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Local Guide 2 Zwolle</string>
    <string-array name="tab_fest">Festivity,</string-array>
    <string-array name="tabs">
        <item>Festivity</item>
        <item>Restaurants</item>
        <item>Museums</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="example">example text</string>
    <!--String for subject image-->
    <string name="subject_image">This image displays the essence of the location</string>
    <!--String for location-->
    <string name="location">Click on this icon to guide you to the location</string>
    <!--String to call the location-->
    <string name="call">Click here to make a phone call to the location</string>
    <!--String to email the location-->
    <string name="email">Click here to send an e-mail to the location</string>
    <!--String for Play button-->
    <string name="play_pause">Play button for audio fragment</string>


    <!--FestivityFragments StringArrays-->

    <string-array name="liberation_festival">
        <item>Liberation Festival Overijssel</item>
        <item>Festival Overijssel Zwolle
            \nEvery May 5th the largest liberation festival in the Netherlands happens in Zwolle with more
            than 50 performances and more than 130,000 visitors. The festival on May 5th. with
            various venues, more than dozens of performances, hundreds of volunteers and many
            substantive projects, the festival is worth a visit!
            \nStarting at the Main Stage? Or first along the Danstheater? The choice is overwhelming.
            \nWould you like to sing along with the famous hits like \'\'A Million Ways\'\', \'\'Say
            Heaven Say
            Hell\'\' and \'\'Wish I Could\'\'. This is possible, because Miss Montreal will also
            perform again this year at the liberation festival Overijssel.</item>
        <item>Office Liberation Festival Overijssel \nCeintuurbaan 15 \n8022 AW Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4532660</item>
        <item>info@bevrijdingsfestivaloverijssel.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city_festival">
        <item>City festival Zwolle</item>
        <item>The City Festival is a multi-day theater festival with a varied selection of music,
            theater, dance, opera, food and drinks in Zwolle.
            \nThe festival transforms the Noordereiland, next to Theater De Spiegel, into a lively festival site.
            \nMore information on the website: www.stadsfestival.nl"</item>
        <item>Office City festival \nSpinhuisplein 14 \n8011 ZZ Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4288280</item>
        <item>info@stadsfestival.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="zwolle_unlimited">
        <item>Zwolle Unlimited</item>
        <item>At the Brothers church square Three days full of stories, street theater and
            music. And on Sundays the Zwolle book market.
            \nZwolle Unlimited has in recent years developed into a defining festival in the
            field of national and international storytelling theater, and related linguistic
            disciplines. With top international street theater and with a nice nose for music as
            a retiring program around the stories. All this brought in the intimate, atmospheric
            setting of the historic city center of Zwolle. No festival \'out of packages and
            bags\', but \'prepared\' with pure, natural ingredients or: the artisan, pure art.
            \nEntrance: via valuation afterwards. You give after every performance what it is
            worth to you, nothing more but nothing less. You can pay with money and with festival
            coins.</item>
        <item>Office Zwolle Unlimited (De Verhalenboot)
            \nPletterstraat 20
            \n8011 VG Zwolle</item>
        <item>06&#8211;50252300</item>
        <item>organisatie@zwolleunlimited.nl</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--MuseumsFragment StringArrays-->

    <string-array name="museum_the_foundation">
        <item>Museum the Foundation</item>
        <item>Come and see this extensive museum, it is definitely worth it!
            \nPalace at the Blijmarkt is the location of Museum de Foundation in Zwolle.
            \nThis neoclassical building was built between 1838 and 1841, after a design by the
            Hague architect Eduard Louis de Coninck. It served as the Palace of Justice and later
            hosted, among other things, the Provincial Planning Service.
            \nIn 2004/2005 the Palace at the Blijmarkt was converted into an art museum after a
            design by architect Gunnar Daan. Since June 2005, the Palace and the Het Nijenhuis
            Museum have formed the Fundatie. On the ground floor there is an extensive choice
            from the museum\'s own collection of visual art, from the late Middle Ages to the
            present.
            \nThis collection was mainly brought together by collector Dirk Hannema (1895-1984,
            former director Boymans Museum in Rotterdam) and includes works by old masters such
            as Strozzi, Vroom and Weenix, international masterpieces by Picabia, Turner, Bernini
            and Canova and many Dutch art from, among others, Mondrian, Israel, Toorop, van der
            Leck, Apple, Lucebert, Carter and many others. On the top floor, regularly changing
            exhibitions are put together.</item>
        <item>Museum the Foundation \nBlijmarkt 20 \n8011 NE Zwolle</item>
        <item>0572&#8211;388188</item>
        <item>info@museumdefundatie.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="herman_brood_experience">
        <item>Herman Brood Experience</item>
        <item>At the Herman Brood Experience we like to give you an insight into the legendary 
            life of the singer and painter who died in 2001. \nPaintings, screen prints and 
            drawings by the artist. Visitors can also look at photos and personal items such as 
            painted guitars, clothing, painting material and even needles.
            \nThe widow of Brood, Xandra, is involved in the project.
            \nVisitors do not have to pay an entrance fee for the Experience, but a voluntary 
            contribution is always welcome. In the shop you can buy paintings, screen prints, 
            drawings and bread merchandise.</item>
        <item>Herman Brood Experience \nBlijmarkt 21 \n8011 ND Zwolle"</item>
        <item>06&#8211;55336540</item>
        <item>info@hermanbroodexperience.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dutch_bakery_museum">
        <item>Dutch Bakery Museum</item>
        <item>The Dutch Bakery museum is in Hattem, near Zwolle.
            \nWhat a nice and delicious museum!
            \nIn the nicest and largest bakery museum in the Netherlands there is a lot to do for
            young and old. In the historic buildings you will find everything about the tasty
            history of bread and pastry. Seeing, tasting, smelling and feeling are of paramount importance.
            \nChildren can bake themselves every day during school holidays. Check our website
            for more baking activities and packages.
            \nWhat a nice and tasty museum!</item>
        <item>Dutch Bakery Museum \nKerkhofstraat 13 \n8051 GG Hattem</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4441715</item>
        <item>info@bakkerijmuseum.nl</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--RestaurantsFragment StringArrays-->

    <string-array name="restaurant_the_librije">
        <item>Restaurant the Librije</item>
        <item>Restaurant the Librije is the restaurant of star chef Jonnie and his wife Thérèse
            \n\'We eat and drink every day, but we are happy to make this daily requirement a
            treat for you, so that you can share our love for good food and fine wines.
            \nWe both grew up in this environment. A world of catching pike-perch, picking
            water-mint, searching for boletus and chanterelles and entering with small boats the duck decoy.
            Hence, is it so strange that we have fallen in love with all those beautiful regional
            products?
            \nMany people call cooking with regional products our specialty, but we think
            that we are special precisely because we do not have a specialty. When you cook and
            serve with heart and soul, from your feeling, everything is special.
            \nTogether with our team we explore every day the possibilities of marrying wine and
            food into a lovely relationship. We want to let you taste the things we discover over
            and over again, to spoil you, without a fuss.\'</item>
        <item>Restaurant the Librije \nSpinhuisplein 1, \n8011 ZZ Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;8530000</item>
        <item>info@librije.com</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bistro_de_kwaak">
        <item>Bistro de Kwaak</item>
        <item>Welcome on board Bistro the Kwaak.
            \nThe freighter which was launched in 1904 was given a second destination in the
            1980s: a sailing theater ship, as many of the Kwaak still know. In the winter of 2017
            we, Andras Schoorl and Carien van Hasselt, gave the ship a third life, Bistro De Kwaak!
            \nWith a view to the traditional character of the ship, a comfortable ship\'s
            compartment has been created with a maximum of 40 seats and 60 pitches. This third
            life is dominated by surprising and pure dishes that are often slightly different
            than normal. Prepared with passion and served with attention in and on the most
            beautiful canal of Zwolle.</item>
        <item>Bistro de Kwaak \nPletterstraat 22 \n8011 VG Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;3377044</item>
        <item>info@dekwaak.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city_brewery_hettinga_beer">
        <item>CITY BREWERY HETTINGA BEER</item>
        <item>Hettinga Bier was founded in January 2008 by Focke Hettinga and Joyce Orsel. The
            brewery initiative was born from the passion for enjoying a good and delicious beer.
            Hettinga Bier is brewed in the traditional way in Zwolle with vitalized water. The
            vitalized water has a positive influence on the taste and quality of the beer. In
            2009 we were elected the hero of the taste for the province of Overijssel for brewing
            regional beers.
            \nWe brew our beer in an authentic way, ie with purely natural raw materials, without
            filtration and pasteurization. All our beers ferment in the bottle which gives the
            beers a full and round taste.</item>
        <item>CITY BREWERY HETTINGA \nEsdoornstraat 3 \n(Dieze west) \n8021 WB Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4662902</item>
        <item>info@hettingabier.nl</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--ShoppingFragment StringArrays-->

    <string-array name="the_zwolle_ball_house">
        <item>"The Zwolle Ball House"</item>
        <item>Walk into the Zwolle Ball House and imagine yourself in grandmother\'s time with the
            sweet scent of traditional old Dutch sweets such as polka chunks and wine balls.
            \nThe real Zwolse Balletjes are made in the traditional way in the cellar of the
            Zwolle Ball House. The recipe is already ancient and still secret.
            \nIn addition, the owner, Wies Dull, is ready to answer questions about Zwolle and
            surroundings from tourists and from residents of Zwolle and to advise all visitors to
            their satisfaction. In addition, at this Tourist Information Point you will find city
            maps with sights, special shopping guides, beautiful city walks and cycle routes
            (free as well as sales material).
            \nYou will also find many Zwolse presents in the Zwolle Ball House, such as Zwols
            food van Zwolse retailers and sells real Zwolle art.
            \nAll this from her passion for Zwolle: Zwolle is a city with allure and Zwolle info
            and gifts wants to do everything to show it!</item>
        <item>The Zwolle Ball House \nGrote Kerkplein 13 \n8011 VA Zwolle,</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4218815</item>
        <item>info@zwolseballetjes.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="waanders_in_the_brothers_church">
        <item>Waanders in the Brothers church</item>
        <item>Waanders In the Brothers church, more than just a book store!
            \nWaanders int the Brothers is divided into \'worlds\'. These worlds show you the way.
            In the worlds you will find books, but also all kinds of accessory articles that fit
            the books on the shelf.
            \nThe cookbooks are combined with tasteful crockery. The travel books are next to
            carefully selected accessories for on the road. The art books are accompanied by
            design articles. In addition to children\'s and youth literature, the children\'s
            department also offers contemporary and imaginative toys.
            \nWith this, Waanders In de Broeren gives a contemporary twist to the phenomenon of
            book trade.</item>
        <item>Waanders in the Brothers church \nAchter de Broeren 1&#8211;3 \n8011 VA Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4215392</item>
        <item>info@waandersindebroeren.nl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meinesz_bennesz">
        <item>Meinesz and Bennesz</item>
        <item>Meinesz and Bennesz in a bird\'s eye view
            \nIt was in the autumn of 1994, on 15 October, that world famous Zwollenaar Ria van
            Ommen Meinesz and Bennesz store opened at Assendorperstraat 169. Zwolle was a unique
            store richer.
            \nMeine Boonstra and Ben van Loo started their hobby first, on Thursday evening and
            Saturday, with the sale of the most diverse brocante, second-hand items. When an
            Assendorper store in wooden toys stopped, Meine and Ben took over the articles.
            \nSoon they grew out of their jacket. After two years they moved to number 82, a bit
            further away in the Assendorperstraat. Everything was possible, everything was sold:
            lamps, religious statues, crates, wind chimes, handicrafts such as custom-made
            tables, candles from a candle maker, pepper boxes from a local artist and the nicest,
            most beautiful gift items. There was a gate of love where couples could walk under,
            there were contests for children and Meine and Ben were always everywhere. Since
            1997, Meine has been the solid Saint of Saints, and his love for the saintly is first
            and foremost in the sale of saints\' images.
            \nIn 2006 Meine and Ben opened the unique, smallest and most fun Sinterklaas Museum
            under the building at number 82. The store turned from yellow to green to orange and
            was used more and more efficiently. The range also changed. In 2011, Meine and Ben
            decided to focus entirely on party items and party clothing. A supersuccess decision:
            since then the storm has been running. Number 33, the building exactly opposite
            number 82, is full of the most diverse party clothes, from carnival costumes to
            lederhosen. If you want to be in the party mood, you should pay a visit to Meinesz and
            Bennesz. For fun and fun!</item>
        <item>Meinesz and Bennesz \nAssendorperstraat 82 en 33 \n8012 CB Zwolle</item>
        <item>038&#8211;4211399</item>
        <item>meineszbennesz@planet.nl</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>

